

DHARANIKUMAR K

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone

+91-9952638437



Email

<u>dharanfsd@gmail.com</u>



Address

Dusi, Kancheepuram, Tamilnadu



MY SKILLS

- O HTML
- ① CSS
- O BOOTSTRAP
- TAILWIND CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- O REACT JS
- NODE JS
- ② EXPRESS JS
- O MY SQL
- MONGO DB



SOCIAL MEDIA

PORTFOLIO

HTTPS://DHARANPORTFOLIO.NET LIFY.APP/

(>) LINKEDIN

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ DHARANIKUMARKFSD/

GITHUB

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/KDHARANI KUMAR



PROFILE INFO

I'm a Mechanical Engineering & MBA Graduate. I have 5 years of experience in the Automobile Industries Quality Department. Now I have to change my career to the Software Industry. So I did the Complete Full Stack Developer (MERN) Course.



EDUCATION

Diploma In Automobile 2009-2011Engineering

Dusi Polytechnic College, Dusi

B.E - Mechanical Engineering 2013-2016 Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College of Engineering. - AMACE Vadamavandhal-Kancheepuram

MBA - Supply Chain Management 2018-2019
 University of Madras - Chennai

8

CERTIFICATION

Full Stack Development (MERN) 2022-2023Guvi - Chennai



WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Trainee2011-2013

Hyundai Mobis - Chennai

Quality Engineer
 Rockman - Cheyyar

Web Design 2018-2019YoukoTech - Chennai

Entrepreneur
STARFLIT- Dusi, Kancheepuram



PROJECTS LINKS

LIBRARY MANAGEMENT
https://librarymanagements.netlify.app/

ADDRESS BOOK https://addressstorebook.netlify.app/

PIZZA APP
https://pizza-client.netlify.app/

FIT LOG
https://fitnesslog.netlify.app/